Guide to the Lydia Lunch Papers MSS.590
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lydia Lunch Papers
1947-2019
1976-2005
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lunch, Lydia
MSS.590
30 linear feet in 39 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 4 record cartons, 2 small flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes, 3 CD boxes, 3 media boxes, and 1 flat-file folder.
56.18 Gigabytes in 4,514 computer files.
11 videocassettes (minidv)
1 sound discs (minidisc)
1 videocassettes (hi8)
3 sound cassettes (dat)
49 audiocassettes
59 videocassettes (vhs)
1 sound tape reels
1 film reels
2 videocassettes (u-matic)
Lydia Lunch (born Lydia Anne Koch, 1959) is an American singer, photographer, writer, actress, and spoken word performer of the New York no wave and punk scene. Lunch founded the no wave band Teenage Jesus and the Jerks with James Chance in 1976, and in her solo career has collaborated with Exene Cervenka, Kim Gordon, Thurston Moore, Nick Cave, No Trend, and the Birthday Party. Lunch records and performs as a spoken word artist with frequent collaborators, and writes literature and underground comix, often with autobiographical content. She has also appeared in films by Richard Kern, Scott B, and Beth B, as well as written, directed, and acted in her own underground films. The Lydia Lunch Papers date from the mid-1940s to 2019 and consist of materials created and collected by Lydia Lunch documenting her artistic career and output as a singer, writer, photographer, actress, and spoken word performer in the New York punk and no wave scenes. Materials include press clippings, press kits, set lists, posters, magazines, performance promotional material, personal journals and notebooks, original writings for songs and spoken word pieces in various stages, commercial audiovisual material, and published writings. A significant portion of the collection is photographs taken by a variety of artists active in the 1970s through 2000s including Christina Birrer, J K Potter, Annie Sprinkle, Sheyla Baykal, Bart Frescura, Michael Levine, and Marc Viaplana. Most of these images are of Lunch taken for album covers and promotional material, but there are also images with others from her artistic circle including Emilio Cubeiro, Exene Cervenka, Henry Rollins, Rowland S Howard, and Nick Cave. Lunch was also a photographer and a large portion of this collection contains her digital and print images, mostly of friends and from her performance touring locations throughout the United States and internationally. A significant amount of analog as well as digital audio and video recordings of Lunch's studio and live performances, both solo and with others are also in this collection dating from the late 1970s to the 2010s. Performances took place in clubs including the Knitting Factory, CBGBs, and the Kitchen in New York City, as well as in international venues in Spain, Germany, Australia, and Poland. The collection also contains the files and audiovisual recordings of friend, film co-star, and fellow spoken word performer Emilio Cubeiro.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Lydia Lunch in October 2019; the accession number associated with this gift is 2019.077.
Appraisal
Duplicate copies of commercial CD or DVD recordings (59 CDs, 2 DVDs, and 4 vhs) were transferred to the New York University Avery Fisher Center For Music and Media.
The following born-digital materials were blank and removed from the collection: FA_MSS_590_107; FA_MSS_590_30; FA_MSS_590_33
Bank statements, medical records, receipts, and duplicate promotional material and clippings were removed from the collection.
Arrangement
Organized into two series:
Series I. Photographs and Work Files
Series II. Performance and Studio Recordings
Biographical Note
Lydia Lunch (born Lydia Anne Koch, 1959) is an American singer, poet, writer, actress, and spoken word performer of the New York no wave and punk scene from the mid-1970s through the 2000s. She founded the no wave band Teenage Jesus and the Jerks with James Chance in 1976, and in her solo career has collaborated with Exene Cervenka, Kim Gordon, Thurston Moore, Nick Cave, No Trend, and the Birthday Party. Lunch records and performs as a spoken word artist, with frequent collaborators, and writes literature and underground comix, often with autobiographical content. She has also appeared in films by Scott B and Beth B, as well as written, directed, and acted in her own underground films.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted.
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Select audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains materials created and collected by Lydia Lunch documenting her artistic career and output as a singer, poet, writer, actress, and spoken word performer in the New York punk and no wave scenes. Press clippings, spoken word performance scripts, setlists, and promotional material for Lunch's performances at various venues around New York and internationally are in this collection, as well as material related to her writing, including project files, lyrics, notebooks, editions of her books in various languages, and manuscripts. There are copies of many of her albums and movies in this collection, which are only available for reference and not for viewing, spanning her entire career from the 1970s to the 2000s. This collection also contains a small amount of material on her friend and fellow spoken word performer, Emilio Cubeiro, some promotional material on Lunch's company Widowspeak, tour contracts and royalty statements, and Lunch family ephemera. This collection also includes photographs of Lunch, friends, and collaborators by various photographers active during the 1980s through 2000s, the majority of which were used for album covers and publicity material.
The largest portion of this collection is photographs created by Lunch dating from the 1990s to the 2000s. Her subjects included places, portraits of children, and images of her friends including Emilio Cubeiro, Gene Gregorits, Debi Mazar, Hubert Selby Jr, Foetus, Jerry Stahl, and Terry Kopenhager. Her photographs explore a variety of themes including simulated bondage, people handling and threatening others with weapons, and self-mutilation. Lunch also took images during her performance tours in the United States and overseas, including Switzerland, Germany, London, Brussels, Paris, Barcelona, New York, and Prague. Lunch's documentation as an actress on various film sets includes digital images from The Heart is Deceitful Above All Things in 2003.
This collection also contains unreleased audio and video performances and studio recordings dating from the mid-1970s to 2010s. These recordings include live performances by Lunch, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, Beirut Slump, and other Lunch collaborators in New York clubs including CBGBs, the Kitchen, and the Knitting Factory, as well as international venues in Spain, Germany, and Australia. This collection also contains recordings from performances by Lunch's friend Emilio Cubeiro and his band Hot Lunch from the 1970s and 1980s This collection has a small number of studio recordings of Lunch's songs.
No wave (Music); Noise music; Punk culture.; Punk rock music.; Women musicians; Women authors, American.; Punk culture and art; Musicians -- 20th century; Authors, American -- 20th century.; Photographers -- United States.; Experimental theater -- 20th century; Avant-garde (Aesthetics) -- United States.; Posters.; Poets, American -- 20th century.; Spoken word poetry, American; Photographs.; Lyricists; Audiocassettes.; VHS; Musicians.; Lunch, Lydia; Beirut Slump (Musical group); Cave, Nick, 1957-; Cubeiro, Emilio; Eight Eyed Spy (Musical group); Teenage Jesus and the Jerks (Musical group); Kern, Richard, 1954-
- Series I. Photographs and Work Files, 1947-2019; 1976-2000; 24 Linear Feet in 39 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 2 small flat boxes, 2 oversize boxes, 1 record carton, and 2 CD boxes; 10 Gigabytes in 4,489 computer files.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographs of and by Lydia Lunch, press clippings, promotional material, writing files and books, spoken word scripts, and reference copies of her albums and movies. This series also contains a small amount of material on her friend Emilio Cubeiro, material from her company Widowspeak, tour contracts and royalty statements, and family ephemera.
  Early Lunch family photographs date from the 1940s to 1960s and also include childhood ephemera. This series also contains files accumulated by Lunch after the death of friend, acting co-star, spoken word performer, and collaborator Emilio Cubeiro. These files include promotion fliers, photographs, and clippings related to Cubeiro's band Hot Lunch and his spoken word performances at CBGBs, the Knitting Club and other venues around New York in the 1970s and 1980s.
  A significant portion of this series is photographs of Lunch by various artists active during the 1970s to 2010s including Christina Birrer, David Arnoff, Beth B, Sheyla Baykal, Bart Frescura, Michael Levine, J K Potter, Annie Sprinkle, and Marc Viaplana. Most of the photographs are portraits of Lunch for publicity and album covers. Some images also include Lunch with her bands, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks and 8 Eyed Spy, as well as fellow artists and collaborators Henry Rollins, Exene Cervenka, Weasel Walter, Nick Cave, Rowland S. Howard, and JG Thirlwell. Lunch acted in a number of Richard Kern movies in the 1980s and photographs from the sets and film stills are in this series. Photographs created by Lunch dating from the 1990s to the 2000s make up the majority of files in this series. Her subject matter includes cemeteries, buildings, children, and images of friends and fellow artists including Emilio Cubeiro, Gene Gregorits, Debi Mazar, Ed and Kathy Joe Kramer, Hubert Selby Jr, Mark Hudson, Chris Hanley, Foetus, Jerry Stahl, Laura Gomel, and Terry Kopenhager. Her photographs are mostly portraits, addressing themes which include bondage, people holding and using weapons on others, sadomasochism, and self-mutilation. Lunch also photographed people and places during her performance tours in the United States and overseas, including Switzerland, Germany, London, Brussels, Paris, Barcelona, New York, and Prague. Lunch's documentation of her work as an actress on various film sets includes digital images from The Heart is Deceitful Above All Things in 2003. Both the photographs of Lunch and by Lunch often contain themes related to bondage, sadism, self-harming, sexuality, and rape.
  This series contains a sampling of Lunch's commercial video and audio recordings which have been retained for reference and not for viewing. These objects include record albums for Teenage Jesus and Jerks, Richard Kern movies, Lunch's albums, and other albums in which she collaborated or contributed to. Design proofs for CDs and DVDs from various projects are in this series, some relating to albums produced by her company, Widowspeak. This series also includes Widowspeak promotional brochures and announcements. A small number of performance contracts and royalty statements are also in this series.
  The press clippings date from the 1970s to 2010s and include Lunch appearance announcements, performance and book reviews, and profiles on Lunch and her work. Posters and promotional fliers and brochures for her spoken word performances, musical performances, movies, book tours, album releases, and other public appearances date from the 1980s to 2019.
  This series includes notebooks and handwritten notes for Lunch's lyric and book ideas, scrapbooks, manuscripts, drafts, and an address book with notes. Files also include plays and illustrated books written with Nick Cave and illustrator Mike Matthews; plays with Emilio Cubeiro; and also material related to her works Psychomenstruum, Paradoxia, Johnny Behind the Deuce, and Diaries of the Sexually Insane. This series also contains Lunch's spoken word performance scripts which included notated lyrics, notes, setlists, and stage directions, dating from the 1990s to 2010s. A small number of individual files throughout this series are on the planning of Lunch's performance touring in New Zealand, Australia, and Europe, including schedules, correspondence, and notes.
  Arrangement
  Files in this series with the same title are grouped together and arranged chronologically within that group.
  - Early Koch Family Photographs and Memorabilia, 1947-1965, undated; cuid30038 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Emilio Cubeiro -- Hot Lunch and Other Performance Promotional Material, Photographs, and Writings, 1960s-1980s; cuid30039 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Photographs by Rick Armstrong -- Lunch and Bart Frescura, undated; cuid30040 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photographs by David Arnoff -- Lunch, Exene Cervenka, Henry Rollins, undated; cuid30041 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Photographs by Beth B -- Lunch, undated; cuid30042 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs by Sheyla Baykal -- South of Your Border Images with Lunch and Emilio Cubeiro, 1988; cuid30043 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs by Christina Birrer -- Lunch, Rowland S Howard, Henry Rollins, undated; cuid30044 (Box 1, Folder 9-11, Box 41, Folder 4-12)
  - Photographs by Marcy Blaustein -- Lunch, undated; cuid30045 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs by Chantal Coves -- "Agony" Cover with Lunch, 1981; cuid30046 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs by Monica Dee -- Lunch with Man, 1985; cuid30047 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs by Angela Egner -- Lunch Performing, undated; cuid30048 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photographs by Bart Frescura -- Lunch, Tom Tully, Olympic/Paris, Torture Museum, 1997-2000, undated; cuid30049 (Box 2, Folder 1-8)
  - Photographs by Petra Gall -- Lunch, undated; cuid30050 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs by Julia Gorton -- Lunch, undated; cuid30051 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs by Peter Gruchot -- Lunch, undated; cuid30052 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs by Lisa Haun -- Lunch, 1984; cuid30053 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs for Richard Kern Movies -- Lunch and Others, 1986, undated; cuid30054 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Photograph by Michael Kennedy and Doris Kloster -- Lunch, undated; cuid30055 (Box 3, Folder 5, Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Photographs by Marcus Leatherdale and Michael Levine -- Lunch, 1986, undated; cuid30056 (Box 3, Folder 6, Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Photographs by Potter / Morris Collaboration -- Proof for Lunch Album, undated; cuid30057 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photographs by David Naz -- Lunch, Unknown Woman Model, undated; cuid30058 (Box 3, Folder 8, Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Photographs by Doralba Picerno -- Lunch, undated; cuid30059 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photographs by J.K. Potter -- Lunch and Other Models, circa 1993, undated; cuid30060 (Box 3, Folder 10, Box 42, Folder 5-6, Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Photographs by Manfred Rahs and Marcia Resnick -- Lunch, 1984, 1990s-2000s; cuid30061 (Box 3, Folder 11, Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Photographs by Ali Smith -- Lunch, 1999; cuid30062 (Box 3, Folder 12, Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Photographs by Annie Sprinkle -- Lunch, undated; cuid30063 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photographs by Chris Stein -- Honeymoon in Red Album Images, circa 1987; cuid30064 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photographs by Stevenson -- Lunch, 1979; cuid30065 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photographs by David Stoltz -- Lunch, undated; cuid30066 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photographs by Wim Van De Hulst -- Lunch and Other Models, undated; cuid30067 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photographs by Marc Viaplana -- Lunch, Elevator, undated; cuid30068 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Lunch by Various Photographers, 1970s to 2000s; cuid30069 (Box 3, Folder 19, Box 4, Folder 1-7, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Photographs of Lunch with Women Bandmates, Exene Cervenka, Bart Frescura, circa 1980s; cuid30070 (Box 4, Folder 8, Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs of Lunch with Weasel Walter, Nick Cave, Rowland S Howard, Eight Eyed Spy, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, and Other Friends, 1990s-2010s; cuid30071 (Box 5, Folder 3-8, Box 42, Folder 1-2, Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Commercial Lydia Lunch Recordings, 1978-2016, undated; cuid30072 (Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46)
  - Press Clippings, 1970s-2010s; cuid30073 (Box 5, Folder 9-12, Box 6, Folder 1-5, Box 7, Box 8, Folder 1-2, Box 40, Folder 2-3, Box 41)
  - Lyrics and Album Images, 1980s-1998; cuid30074 (Box Electronic Record, E-records FA_MSS_590_ER_5)
  - Promotional Material, Posters, Event Programs, 1980s-2021; cuid30075 (Box 8, Folder 3-7, Box 9, Folder 1-5, Box 10)
  - Promotional Material -- Posters, 1980s-2021; cuid30287 (Box 40, Folder 1, 9-10, Box 41, Folder 1, Box 54, Folder 1, 11-12, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Writings -- Lyrics, 1980-1995; cuid30076 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Writings -- Adulterers Anonymous Proofs and Book, 1982; cuid30077 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Writings -- Illustrated Book Projects with Nick Cave and Mike Matthews, 1985-1993; cuid30078 (Box 10, Folder 9-10, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Writings -- Plays Written with Nick Cave and Tottenham, 1985; cuid30079 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Writings -- Manuscripts, Notes, Submissions, 1986-1987; cuid30080 (Box 11, Folder 4-6)
  - Writings -- South of Your Borders Manuscript Written with Emilio Cubeiro, 1988; cuid30081 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Writings -- Articles, Contributions, Drafts, 1989-1998; cuid30082 (Box 11, Folder 8-9, Box 12, Folder 3-7)
  - Writings -- Psychomenstruum Manuscript Written with John Duffy, 1990; cuid30083 (Box 11, Folder 10-11, Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- Incriminating Evidence -- English and German Editions of the Book, 1992, 2000; cuid30084 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Writings -- Paradoxia -- Drafts, Promotional Material, English and Foreign Language Editions of the Book, 1997-2011; cuid30085 (Box 12, Folder 8, Box 13, Folder 1-7)
  - Writings -- Paradoxia -- Press Kit, 2005; cuid30086 (Box Electronic Record, E-records FA_MSS_590_ER_6)
  - Writings -- Devil's Racetrack -- Manuscript, 1998-1999; cuid30087 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- Preacher Written with Ted McKeever, 1999; cuid30088 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Writings -- Vicera Short Story, 2000; cuid30089 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Writings -- Johnny Behind the Deuce -- Drafts, 2000-2001; cuid30090 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - Writings -- Sex and Guts Written with Gene Gregorits -- Advertisement List, circa 2000-2003; cuid30091 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Writings -- Panties by David Naz, with Introduction by Lunch, 2002; cuid30092 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Writings -- Amnesia -- Proof, Book, and Related, 2009-2010; cuid30093 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
  - Writings -- Will Work for Drugs -- Czech and German Editions of the Book, 2009, 2011; cuid30094 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Writings -- Drafts, Manuscripts, Lyrics, 2018, undated; cuid30095 (Box 15, Folder 2-6)
  - Notebooks with Notes and Ideas, Address Book, Diary, Scrapbooks, 1988-2003, undated; cuid30096 (Box 15, Folder 7-8, Box 16, Folder 1-6)
  - Covers for Video, DVD, and CD Recording Cases, 1981-2010; cuid30097 (Box 16, Folder 7-11)
  - Contracts and Royalties, 1982-2013; cuid30098 (Box 17, Folder 1-9)
  - Diaries of the Sexually Insane -- Performance Scripts, Letter Contributions, 1985-1995; cuid30099 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
  - Widowspeak Productions -- Notes, Promotional Material, Press Releases, History, Video Covers, 1985-2007; cuid30100 (Box 19, Folder 1-6)
  - Friend's Artworks, Memorabilia, 1987-1988, 2004, undated; cuid30101 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Torso Exhibition -- Notes, Images, early 1990s; cuid30102 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Cemeteries, Graveyards, Burning Building, Torsos, 1990-1995; cuid30103 (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Australia, Prague, Madrid, Mark, Bart, Kat, 1994-1998; cuid30104 (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Mark, Kat, McKeesport, Cemetery, Bart, Rogers Flea Market, circa 1996-1998; cuid30105 (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs by Lunch --JGT, Emilio Cubeiro Vermont, Egypt, Leo, Vanessa / Serbian Church, circa 1996-1998; cuid30106 (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Kathy Jo Kramer Bus, Ed Kramer, Leo, Ramona and Jane, Oslo, circa 1996-1998; cuid30107 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Switzerland, Paris, Germany, Prague, London, Selby, Ian, Laila, Vanessa, Pittsburgh, circa 1997-2001; cuid30108 (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Pleasant, Barcelona, Bern, US Tour, Loren, France, Color Tour, Mark Hudson, Rick, Bart, JG, Mia, 1997-1998; cuid30109 (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Mark Hudson and Rick, Rochester / Vanessa, Gene, Tour, Italy, 1998-1999; cuid30110 (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Tour, White Edwards, Kelly, Shadow, Jerry, Paul and Claudio, KAK, KJ, 1999-2000; cuid30111 (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Selby Jr., Laila, Torsos, Smelly Guilt, Emilio Cubeiro, Elvis and Stacey, Shooting Range, 2000-2006, undated; cuid30112 (Box 28, Folder 1-9)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Harrisburg / Foetus, Margaret, Madge, Steve, Vanessa, Gillian, 1990s-2000s; cuid30113 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Jerry Stahl, Julie and Ed, Adult Motel Versailles, Leo, Detroit, Jane / Gypsy, Palermo, 1990s-2000s; cuid30114 (Box 30, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Laura Gomel, Voodoo Dolls, Backyard, Brent, Prague, Rick as Ray, Claudio, Rick, 1990s-2000s; cuid30115 (Box 31, Folder 1-5)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Gene Gregorits, Gene and Carmi, Portraits, Debi Mazar, Greece, Humbolt, 1990s-2000s; cuid30116 (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Claudio, European Tour, Munich, Paris, Sabine, Poland, Bern, Terry Kopenhager, 1990s-2000s; cuid30117 (Box 33, Folder 1-5, Box 34, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs by Lunch -- Unidentified Images, 1990s-2000s; cuid30118 (Box 34, Folder 3-6, Box 35, Folder 1-4, Box 39, Folder 11-13, Box 40, Folder 4-7, Box 42, Folder 8-19, Box 54, Folder 4-7, 13, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Photographs by Lunch and Marc Viaplana, undated; cuid30119 (Box 54, Folder 8-10)
  - Correspondence, 1991-2000; cuid30120 (Box 35, Folder 5-8, Box 36, Folder 1-5)
  - Australian Tour Documentation, 1994; cuid30121 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Fan Art, 1995-1998; cuid30122 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Spoken Word Performance Scripts and Set Lists, 1999-2015, undated; cuid30123 (Box 36, Folder 9-10, Box 37, Folder 1-10, Box 38, Folder 1-12)
  - Lunch and Gene Gregorits Spoken Word Performance Material, 2000; cuid30124 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Images for Album and Video Covers, 2001; cuid30125 (Box Electronic Record, E-records FA_MSS_590_ER_3)
  - Lunch and Marc Viaplana -- Forensic Exhibit Material, circa 2001-2006; cuid30126 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Anubian Nights -- Press Material, 2002-2003; cuid30127 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Willing Victim European Tour Material, 2003; cuid30128 (Box 39, Folder 4)